# Bhrugu Tundeliya

**LinkedIn**: www.linkedin.com/in/bhrugu-tundeliya **Portfolio**: https://portfolio-bhrugu.vercel.app/

Github: https://github.com/Bhrugu14

StackOverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/7034453/bhrugu-tundeliya

115/16 Shyam Tenament Manjipura Road, Nadiad 387001

**(91) 8460304001** 

☑ bhrugu1409@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

A passionate professional and a fast learner; years of working experience of software design principles and agile development principles. worked independently as well as in a team for projects. Having experience in mobile and web development

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Technostacks Infotech Pvt Ltd**, Ahmedabad — *Software Developer* 

July 2022 - PRESENT

## **Codentic software,** Anand — *React Developer*

October 2020 - June 2022

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **Grocery Application**— react native, typescript

Responsible for creating user and delivery partner's application from the scratch, Implemented Family mode that handles group purchase, implemented Razorpay API

# **Catalog Application (Mobile and Website)** — *Next.js, nodejs, React Native*

Build a Mobile responsive website for product catalog with a modern eye-catching design. Working with the remote backend team for development. Integrated MirrAR Ar web plug-in for the try-on feature.

# **E-commerce sweets selling website** — *Next.js, nodejs*

Responsible for bug fixes and design changes on the already developed website, rework on payment modules with different payment methods and promo code integration.

## **BLE Connector** — React Native, Typescript

Created a Mobile application that can detect certain service UUID and connect to it, send and receive messages via BLE.

#### **Online Documents Storage** — React is, Ionic

Responsible for client communication information gathering, design, and development of the project, managed role-based scenarios in folder options, implemented reminder features with different kinds ranges.

# **Rewards-Driven Application** — React Native

Independently designed and developed the Front end of a mobile application, that detects users in close proximity of the vendor's application with Socket, Vendor can send customer-related offers with that. implemented one-signal for notification

#### Online Menu, Promo QRCode generation, Club Application—

React Native, Next js

worked on an online menu project that gets dynamic URLs from QRcode, generates Lottery QRcode with vendor's admin panel, and also bug fixes on clubbing Application for Germany.

#### **SKILLS**

- React
- Next
- lonic
- React Native
- Html
- Css
- Javascript
- Redux
- Mobx
- Typescript

#### **Familiar**

- Vue
- Android
- Nodejs
- Express
- iOS

#### **TOOLS**

- Vscode
- Android Studio
- Xcode

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Hindi
- Gujarati

#### **EDUCATION**

Birla Vishvakarma Mahavidyalaya (BVM), Anand — Computer Engineering — July 2013 - December 2020.